Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Newsletters, 1991-2020; 3; 3.0 cubic ft.
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 29, Numbers 1-3, 2019 January-March (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 29, Numbers 4-6, 2019 April-June (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 29, Numbers 7-9, 2019 July-September (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 29, Numbers 10-12, 2019 October-December (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 30, Numbers 1-3, 2020 January-March (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 30, Numbers 4-6, 2020 April-June (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 30, Numbers 7-9, 2020 July-September (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 30, Numbers 10-12, 2020 October-December (Box 3, Folder 20)